This color suits you very well.
هذا اللون يناسبك جيدًا.
Are you satisfied?
هل أنت راض؟
This fabric is nice,
هذا النسيج جميل ،
this dress is okay,
هذا الفستان على ما يرام ،
Come and take a look.
وتعالوا نلقي نظرة.
This is a black shop.
هذا متجر أسود.
The clothes I bought yesterday
الملابس التي اشتريتها بالأمس
are like this today.
مثل هذا اليوم.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
The quality of clothes in our shop has always been very good,
لطالما كانت جودة الملابس في متجرنا جيدة جدًا ،
but here's the truth,
ولكن ها هي الحقيقة ،
Do you still want to default?
هل ما زلت تريد التخلف عن السداد؟
You.
أنت.
What's wrong?
ماالخطب؟
She said,
قالت ،
the clothes she bought in our store yesterday,
الملابس التي اشترتها في متجرنا بالأمس ،
That's what happened today.
هذا ما حدث اليوم.
Well,
نحن سوف،
Let me take a look at the clothes
اسمحوا لي أن ألقي نظرة على الملابس
first. This guest,
أول.  هذا الضيف ،
Calm down.
اهدأ.
If there is something wrong with our clothes,
إذا كان هناك شيء خاطئ في ملابسنا ،
we will be responsible for it.
سنكون مسؤولين عن ذلك.
Let me have a look first.
دعني ألقي نظرة أولا.
Boss,
رئيس،
the show is starting.
العرض يبدأ.
This dress doesn't belong to us.
هذا الفستان لا يخصنا.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Gosh,
يا الهي ،
profiteers are bullying us ordinary people,
المستفيدون يتنمرون علينا كأشخاص عاديين ،
Is there any law left?
هل بقي أي قانون؟
You don't have to spill it here.
ليس عليك سكبها هنا.
Since I said this dress is not ours,
منذ أن قلت هذا الفستان ليس لنا ،
of course it's because we have evidence,
بالطبع لأن لدينا أدلة ،
Ladies and gentlemen at the scene,
سيداتي وسادتي في المكان ،
please witness with me.
ارجوك شاهد معي.
Yes.
نعم.
Shopkeeper Su,
صاحب متجر سو ،
don't you want evidence?
الا تريد الدليل
Where is the evidence?
أين الدليل؟
Please calm down,
من فضلك اهدأ ،
I don't believe you can get through it safely.
لا أعتقد أنه يمكنك تجاوزها بأمان.
Look,
نظرة،
the clothes in our shop,
الملابس في متجرنا ،
It has the unique logo
لها شعار فريد
of our large size women's clothing store,
من متجرنا لبيع الملابس النسائية كبيرة الحجم ،
But this dress
لكن هذا الفستان
is not very obvious,
ليس واضحًا جدًا ،
These are not our clothes.
هذه ليست ملابسنا.
My lady, you're amazing.
سيدتي ، أنت مدهشة.
How could there be a woman like her?
كيف يمكن أن تكون هناك امرأة مثلها؟
Strong confidence.
ثقة قوية.
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Wu Yue,
وو يو ،
come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Okay Boss,
مدرب بخير،
I want to show you today's account.
اريد ان اريك حساب اليوم.
Be careful
كن حذرا
Boss, you're so powerful.
أنت قوي جدا يا رئيس.
Is my spring coming?
هل ربيعي قادم؟
Jinxia,
جينشيا ،